Frances Ryan Thomas
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Frances Ryan Thomas, 2.1.3.3.2
  - Frances Ryan Thomas: Friends and family, circa early 1900s - 1915; 5 (Box 1521)
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Child and dog outside of house], 45
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Group of children standing outside of house], 46
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Group of people standing outside of small house (school?)], 47
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man leaning against tree], 48
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man and woman in woods], 49
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Three men standing together with woman and mule (?)], 50
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Little girl riding on a mule underneath a sign that reads "DamfinoVI"], 51
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Two women (one Francis Ryan Thomas?) and two men sitting on steps], 52
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Close-up of woman's face (Francis Ryan Thomas?)], 53
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man and woman outside, formally dressed], 54
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Woman (Francis Ryan Thomas?) and man outside of house], 55
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Two children sitting], 56
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Two people mounted on horses (faces cut-off from picture)] Now please don't laugh - you should hear them talk about my horse, 57
    - Verso: Now please don't laugh - you should hear them talk about my horse, 57-verso
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Woman on dirt road lined with trees], 58
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Water], 59
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas; Friends and family: Man and woman sitting in hay with dog], 60
  - Frances Ryan Thomas: Landscape photographs found with Frances Ryan Thomas's personal papers, undated; 6 (Box 1521)
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: River running between mountains], 1
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Sun hitting mountain sides], 2
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Water near mountain side], 3
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: View of mountains], 4
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Aerial view of land], 5
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: View of mountains and pine trees], 6
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Large rock balancing], 7
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: View of mountains and pine trees], 8
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: View of river running by mountains and pine trees], 9
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Pine trees and mountain], 10
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Pine trees and mountain], 11
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Mountains], 12
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Running water near mountain], 13
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Pine trees and mountains], 14
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Running water near mountain], 15
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Water near mountain side, man on rock], 16
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Running water near mountain], 17
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Creek running near pine trees], 18
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Running water near mountain], 19
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Horizon], 20
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Pine trees against cloudy sky], 21
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Dirt road lined with pine trees], 22
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Bushes and pine trees], 23
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Snowy land], 24
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: View of pine trees], 25
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Water running over rocks], 26
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Water running over rocks], 27
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Rushing water over rocks. Bridge], 28
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Waterfall and bridge], 29
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Dirt road lined with pine trees], 30
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Dirt road lined with pine trees], 31
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Waterfall and bridge], 32
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Rock formation], 33
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Waterfall], 34
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: View of campsite (?)], 35
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Fallen trees over water], 36
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Icy water, snowy land], 37
  - Frances Ryan Thomas: Photographs found with Frances Ryan Thomas's personal papers [some hand-colored photographs], undated; 7 (Box 1521)
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Tree woman. One holding a decorative umbrella, another woman bowing at the feet of the other woman], 1
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Two women bowing to each other], 2
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Woman looking in mirror], 3
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Village], 4
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Snowcapped mountain in the distance], 5
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Little sailboat on water], 6
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Snowcapped mountain in the distance], 7
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Two little children walking down a path that leads to house], 8
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Little sailboat on water], 9
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Snowcapped mountain], 10
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Little girl petting dalmation], 11
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Portrait of a woman], 12
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Portrait of a man], 13
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Man petting a dog], 14
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Little house], 15
    - Caption: Do you remember when we first met at a dance dressed as this?, 16
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Four little girls around trees], 17
  - Frances Ryan Thomas: Photographs found with Frances Ryan Thomas's personal papers, circa 1915 - 1920s; 8 (Box 1521)
    - Lowell Thomas, 1
    - Miss Helen Arnold, the movie actress and myself. Taken on the Bridge of the S.S. Chicago. With life-preservers on [August - September 1917], 2
    - Verso: Miss Helen Arnold, the movie actress and myself. Taken on the Bridge of the S.S. Chicago. With life-preservers on [August - September 1917], 2-verso
    - On the "Chicago" - during a life-preserver drill. Mrs. Arnold is with me. She was on her way to Naples to be in a movie. The man has an unsinkable suit on [August - September 1917], 3
    - Verso: On the "Chicago" - during a life-preserver drill. Mrs. Arnold is with me. She was on her way to Naples to be in a movie. The man has an unsinkable suit on [August - September 1917], 3-verso
    - A sunset over the Seine River. Trocadero spires in the back. Eiffel Tower to left, 4
    - Verso: A sunset over the Seine River. Trocadero spires in the back. Eiffel Tower to left, 4-verso
    - "We're going to get the boys out of the trenches by Christmas", 5
    - Verso: "We're going to get the boys out of the trenches by Christmas", 5-verso
    - Vive la Parisienne! [2 copies], 6
    - Verso: Vive la Parisienne!, 6-verso
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Three men, a woman and a dog outside of a tent], 7
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Two men talking], 8
    - In the courtyard of what was the Kaiser's Palace on the Mt of Olives. It was taken during the reception which the new High Commissioner, Sir Herbert Samuel, gave. The statue is of the Kaiser dressed as a Crusader, 9
    - Verso: In the courtyard of what was the Kaiser's Palace on the Mt of Olives. It was taken during the reception which the new High Commissioner, Sir Herbert Samuel, gave. The statue is of the Kaiser dressed as a Crusader, 9-verso
    - A street scene in Jaffa, Palestine, 10
    - Verso: A street scene in Jaffa, Palestine, 10-verso
    - Quite a load, 11
    - Verso: Quite a load, 11-verso
    - Caption: 3 [illegible] Tomb, 12
    - A beggar woman in Jerusalem, 13
    - Verso: A beggar woman in Jerusalem, 13-verso
    - A Jerusalem Jew, farmer, 14
    - Verso: A Jerusalem Jew, farmer, 14-verso
    - On the beach at Aberdeen Scotland [circa 1920], 15
    - Verso: On the beach at Aberdeen Scotland [circa 1920], 15-verso
    - This is Sir William Jury's car which he loans us on Sundays, Isn't it a beauty? Mr. Cummingham is acting as business Mgr. He is now in Scotland trying to arrange a tour for us, before we return, 16
    - Verso: This is Sir William Jury's car which he loans us on Sundays, Isn't it a beauty? Mr. Cummingham is acting as business Mgr. He is now in Scotland trying to arrange a tour for us, before we return, 16-verso
    - Off for a Rickshaw ride at Colombo. My how hot it was! [circa 1921 - 1922], 17
    - Verso: Off for a Rickshaw ride at Colombo. My how hot it was! [circa 1921 - 1922], 17-verso
    - A friend of ours who belongs to the Scottish regiment of The Black Watch - Colombo Ceylon [circa 1921 - 1922], 18
    - Verso: A friend of ours who belongs to the Scottish regiment of The Black Watch - Colombo Ceylon [circa 1921 - 1922], 18-verso
    - A terrible picture of me-but taken in Shalimar gardens where the Indian Love-lyrics were written-near Lahore [circa 1921 - 1922], 19
    - Verso: A terrible picture of me-but taken in Shalimar gardens where the Indian Love-lyrics were written-near Lahore [circa 1921 - 1922], 19-verso
    - Two of the sacred monkeys. There were hundreds around me but Tommy only got two in this picture [circa 1921 - 1922], 20
    - Verso: Two of the sacred monkeys. There were hundreds around me but Tommy only got two in this picture [circa 1921 - 1922], 20-verso
    - This is an example of a child marriage-the girl is 8-the boy 10 and they have been married 3 years [circa 1921 - 1922], 21
    - Verso: This is an example of a child marriage-the girl is 8-the boy 10 and they have been married 3 years [circa 1921 - 1922], 21-verso
    - How would you like a slice of bread? [circa 1921 - 1922], 22
    - Verso: How would you like a slice of bread? [circa 1921 - 1922], 22-verso
    - Bathing along the Ganges [circa 1921 - 1922], 23
    - Verso: Bathing along the Ganges [circa 1921 - 1922], 23-verso
    - A northern type. His vest is embroidered with gold thread. He is a rich merchant [circa 1921 - 1922], 24
    - Verso: A northern type. His vest is embroidered with gold thread. He is a rich merchant [circa 1921 - 1922], 24-verso
    - This is a llama man (priest) from Lhasa, Thibet - Taken in Darjeeling [circa 1921 - 1922], 25
    - Verso: This is a llama man (priest) from Lhasa, Thibet - Taken in Darjeeling [circa 1921 - 1922], 25-verso
    - This is our luggage arriving at Frere Hall, Karachi. By the direction of the shafts of the camel cart it looks as if it were going heavenward. Tommy and Cummingham are standing on the right [circa 1921 - 1922], 26
    - Verso: This is our luggage arriving at Frere Hall, Karachi. By the direction of the shafts of the camel cart it looks as if it were going heavenward. Tommy and Cummingham are standing on the right [circa 1921 - 1922], 26-verso
    - A scene in Karachi. These people spread a few articles out in the street and "set up shop" [circa 1921 - 1922], 27
    - Verso: A scene in Karachi. These people spread a few articles out in the street and "set up shop" [circa 1921 - 1922], 27-verso
    - T.R. [Theodore Roosevelt] and one of his Kenya elephants, 28
    - Verso: T.R. [Theodore Roosevelt] and one of his Kenya elephants, 28-verso
    - Kermit [Roosevelt?] and the first week's trophies, 29
    - Verso: Kermit [Roosevelt?] and the first week's trophies, 29-verso
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Little girl in ballet shoes, on point], 30
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Man and woman holding each other in front of pond], 31
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Baby trying to climb stairs], 32
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Baby sitting on steps], 33
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Baby in a hat], 34
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Baby holding hands], 35
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Baby], 36
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Boy playing in sprinklers], 37
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Three children], 38
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Boy with hands on his knees], 39
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Three women and a little boy], 40
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Person holding baby], 41
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Man holding a bucket], 42
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Parked car], 43
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Man standing next to car], 44
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Little boy standing outside of house], 45
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Woman holding baby in her lap], 46
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Six children sitting on a blanket], 47
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Man holding baby], 48
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Baby on steps], 49
    - [Frances Ryan Thoams Personal Papers: Baby sitting on steps], 50
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Two children outside], 51
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Baby resting on pillow], 52
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Three children outside], 53
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Three children outside], 54
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Little boy hugging little girl], 55
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Little boy and girl sitting on steps], 56
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Little boy standing outside], 57
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Close-up of little boy], 58
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Little boy playign in sprinkler], 59
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Baby sitting on car door], 60
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas Personal Papers: Baby sitting on woman's lap], 61
  - Frances Ryan Thomas: Trip to Europe and Russia, circa 1926; 9 (Box 1521)
    - Moscow, Kremlin and Red Palace, 1
    - Verso: Moscow, Kremlin and Red Palace, 1-verso
    - Moscow with Wassilij Cathedral, 2
    - Verso: Moscow with Wassilij Cathedral, 2-verso
    - Moscow street leading to Aerodrome, 3
    - Verso: Moscow street leading to Aerodrome, 3-verso
    - Aerodrome and wharf of the Deruluft in Konigsberg, 4
    - Verso: Aerodrome and wharf of the Deruluft in Konigsberg, 4-verso
    - View of Kowno with Njemen River, 5
    - Verso: View of Kowno with Njemen River, 5-verso
    - Town view of Kowno with Cathedral, 6
    - Verso: Town view of Kowno with Cathedral, 6-verso
    - Town view of Danzig with Cathedral, 7
    - Verso: Town view of Danzig with Cathedral, 7-verso